[Shivansh Tiwari]



I am Looking forward for an opportunity where I can utilize and finish up my knowledge and skills. Where I can contribute to the firm and make the of my potential and contribute to the organization growth.

Work Experience:-

1

Zet (Previously OneCode) {Vistas Technolabs PVT LTD}

Job Role: Sale of Credit card, Personal Loan, saving and current

Accounts

Office Location: Bangalore Karnataka India (Remote)

Designation: Business Consultant

CIN No.: U93090DIL

Employment Type : Part Time

Working Duration: Dec 2021 To May 2022 (6 Month)

Skill Used : Sales & Lead Generation **Partner ID :** One@shivansh97tiwari

2 Vinay F Kothari Firm (CA).

Job Role: Accounting, Taxation, Audit & Finance

Name : Ajay Pandey (CA). Employment Type : Part Time

Office Location: FB 2/1, B Block, Shilpi Plaza Rewa (On-site) Working Duration: Feb 2019 To Sept 2020 (1 year 8 Month)

Designation : Accountant **Skill Used :** Tally, Financial Accounting & Audit

3 Aditya Birla Sun Life Insurance Company Limited

Job Role : Sale of Life Insurance Product **Employment Type :** Part Time

Office Location : Near new bus stand Rewa (On-site)

Working Duration : Apr 2018 To Jan 2019 (10 Month)

Designation : Insurance Agent

Skill Used : Life Insurance, Finance, Microsoft Excel

CIN No.: U99999MH2000PLC128110 **Advisor Code**: BSLBW4079

Internship:-

1 Sport For All (SFA) Sporting Service Pvt. Ltd

Job Role: Field Work (Helped in organizing the championship and business development)

Office Location : Vijay Nagar Indore, (On-site) Employment Type : Internship

Designation: Sales & Business Development **Working Duration**: July 2023 To Oct 2023 (03 Month)

CIN No.: U74999MH2015PTC268781 Skill Used: Business analyst, Mx excel, Sales, Digital Marketing

2 Vijay Rathi and Company (CA)

Job Role: Account, Taxation, Audit

Name: Rathi Vijaykumar Bhagchandji (CA). Employment Type: Internship

Office Location: 312-313 Hindi Sahitya Bhawan Madhu Milan

Square Indore (On-site)

Working Duration: Nov 2019 To May 2022 (2 year 7 Month)

Designation : Chartered Accountant Assistant **Skill Used :** Smart Tax, Auditing, Accounting & Tax Audits

Education Qualification:-

1

IPS Academy

Degree : PGDM / M.B.A (Marketing & finance) **Status or Grade :** Perusing

University: Devi Ahilya Vishwavidyalaya, Indore Course Duration: Oct 2022 To Oct 2024 (2 year)

2 The Institute of Chartered Accountants of India

Registration of Branch: Indore **Course Duration**: Aug 2019 To Aug 2022 (3 year)

3 Pentium Point Technical College

Degree: B.Com Hons (Account) **Status or Grade**: 62.43

University: Awadhesh Pratap Singh University, Rewa Course Duration: Apr 2016 To Apr 2019 (3 year)

4 National Skill Development Corporation

Degree : Insurance Agent (skill India) Status or Grade : Second Division

University: Pradhan Mantri Kaushal Kendra, Rewa Course Duration: Jan 2019 To Mar 2019 (3 Month)

5 **Central Board of Secondary Education**

School Name: Bal Bharti School

Class: 12th Commerce **Course Duration :** Apr 2015 To Mar 2016 (1 Year)

Status or Grade: 60.20

Central Board of Secondary Education

School Name: Bal Bharti School Status or Grade: 62.00

Class: 10th All Subject Course Duration: Apr 2013 To Mar 2014 (1 Year)

Certifications:-

6

- Mastering Big Data Analytics :- Great Learning (2023)
- A2Z of Stock Trading In Hindi :- Elearn Market (2023) \rightarrow
- \rightarrow Basics of Operational Procurement in Supply Chain Management :- Tata Consultancy Services (2023)
- \rightarrow **Industry Readiness Program in Banking and Insurance :-** NSE Academy (2023)
- \rightarrow **Technical Analysis Made Easy:** - Elearn Market (2023)
- Marketing Analysis :- Semrush (2023) \rightarrow
- \rightarrow The Fundamental of Digital Marketing: Google Digital Garage (2023)
- \rightarrow Financial Advisor :- Gromo (2022)
- \rightarrow **Non life Insurance & Health Insurance :-** Turtlemint (2022)
- **Information Technology:-** The Institute of Chartered Accountants of India (2019) \rightarrow
- **Orientation Course:** The Institute of Chartered Accountants of India (2019) \rightarrow

Key Skill:-

Business Analyst, Sales, Business Consultant, Digital Marketing, Financial Analysis, Account Finalisation, Soft Skill, lead Generation, Ca Inter (Drop Out), Return Filling (Income tax, Gst, Tds, Company work), Audit (Tax Audit, Stock Audit, Gst Audit, Concurrent Audit), Taxation (Direct and Indirect Tax), Accounting (Tally & Marg)

It Skill:-

It operation (word, excel, powerpoint, outlook), Software (Tally, Marg, Smart Gst, Smart Tax, Opto Tax), Typing (English and Hindi)

Industrial Visit:-

Industrial Visit at Kores Pvt Ltd where we learned regarding the Supply Chain Management and Procedure of Manufacturing.

Personal Details:-

Father's Name: Mr. Somdhar Tiwari

Mobile No.: 9617325683

Address: Durga Nagar, Rajendra Nagar, Indore (Current) & Bajrang Nagar Rewa (Permanent)

Lauguage: English (Read, write, Speak) & Hindi

(Read, write, Speak)

Mother's Name: Mrs. Sushila Tiwari Email Id: shivansh97tiwari@gmail.com & shivanshtiwari60222.mbaft22@ipsacademy.org

Hobbies: Playing Games(video Game)& Learning

Business World (Dynamic Environment)

Date of birth: September 10, 1998

Social Profile:- https://www.linkedin.com/in/shivansh97tiwari/(Linkedin.com), https://www.naukri.com/mnj/fullProfile (Naukri.com), https://internshala.com/student/resume?detail_source=resume_direct (Internshala) & https://www.secure.instagram.com/shivansh97tiwari/ (Instagram)

About Me:-

I am Shivansh Tiwari, s/o Somdhar Tiwari. I am currently living in Durg Nagar, Indore, and my native place is Rewa. I passed 10th in 2014 at cbse board, then in 2016, I passed 12th in Commerce field at cbse board. After that, I passed in 2019 from B. Com. Hons. (Account), and I also joined Aditya Birla Sun Life Insurance Company as an insurance agent for 10 months, then I switched and joined Vinay F. Kothari and Co. Ca firm worked in the accountant post for 1 year 8 Month. In 2019 Then, after I entered the CA course at intermediate or ipcc, I cleared the 2nd group with Vijay Rathi and Co (Internship). I joined a CA firm and worked as a CA assistant for 2 years and 7 months. Then I entered Zet previously one code company, I worked for Zet previously one code company for 6 months in a business consultant post after in 2022 I did my MBA (Marketing and Finance) from Ips Academy Indore and Simultaneously i am dong internship in Sport For All (SFA) for 3 month.

Declaration:-

The above furnished information is correct and true to the best of my knowledge and beliefs.

Date:	Signature:
Place:	Shivansh Tiwari